

const data = {
  JsIQData: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `1) What is JavaScript?`,
      answer: `JavaScript is the programming language for the web, it can update and change both HTML and CSS and it can also calculate, manipulate and validate data, it is a language that works on the client and server side.`,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `2) What are javascript data types?`,
      answer: `There are two types of data: The primitive data type can only store a single data whereas the object can store colletion of data.`,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `3) What is javascript standard?`,
      answer: `The javascript standard is the ECMAScript`,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `4) What is ECMAScript?`,
      answer: `ECMA is an acronym for the European Computer Manufacturers Association, which develops standards for information technology. It is a general purpose programming language that is implemented in javascript.`,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `5) Which company developed JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Was created by Brendan Eich at Netscape Communications Corporation, for the Netscape navigator web browser.`,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `6) What are non-primitive data types in Java?`,
      answer: `The non-primitive are: Class, Object, Array.`,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `7) What is the use of the let keyword in javascript?`,
      answer: `It is used to handle a data type in a specific scope, for example, in methods. `,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `8) How do you initialize a variable in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `We use assignment operator = for set the value of a variable.`,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `9) How do you declare a variable?`,
      answer: `It is declared using the var, const, and let keywords.`,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `10) What is typeof operator for?`,
      answer: `Typeof operator in JavaScript is an operator used for type checking and returns the data type of the operand passed to it.`,
    },
    // {
    //   id: 11,
    //   question: `¿Qué es concatenar?`,
    //   answer: `Es agregar, vincular o enlazar contenido.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 12,
    //   question: `¿Ejemplo de un dato booleano?`,
    //   answer: `Var variable = false;`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 13,
    //   question: `¿Ejemplo de un operador relacional?`,
    //   answer: `Nos ayuda a comparar expresiones devolviendo un resultado booleano.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 14,
    //   question: `Cual es la diferencia entre = == y ===?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 15,
    //   question: `Los operadores relacionales devuelven siempre un valor?`,
    //   answer: `Tipo booleano`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 16,
    //   question: `De dos ejemplos de operadores aritméticos.`,
    //   answer: `Suma y resta`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 17,
    //   question: `Que es el operador ternario?`,
    //   answer: `Es una condicion`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 18,
    //   question: `Como se llama este operador "!" ?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 19,
    //   question: `Diferencia entre el operador && y el ||?`,
    //   answer: `Con el operador || debe de ejecutarse 1 de las 2 sentencias. Con el operador && debe de ejecutarse las 2 sentencias.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 20,
    //   question: `De un ejemplo de pre incremento?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 21,
    //   question: `Cual es la estructura de un operador ternario o condicional?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 22,
    //   question: `Cuales son los ciclos definidos?`,
    //   answer: `for`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 23,
    //   question: `Cuales son los ciclos indefinidos?`,
    //   answer: `While and do-while`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 24,
    //   question: `Cual es la diferencia entre while y do while?`,
    //   answer: `Con do-while la sentencia que esta dentro del bloque se ejecutara una vez y luego dependera del while si se vuelve a ejecutar o no cuantas veces sea necesario. Con while la sentencia no se ejecutara si no cumple con lo requerido. `,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 25,
    //   question: `Where start the index of the array?`,
    //   answer: `Desde el cero, es el primer indice.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 26,
    //   question: `What are arrays?`,
    //   answer: `Es un tipo de dato objeto que almacena datos este teniendo un indice interno. `,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 27,
    //   question: `Que son los métodos?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 28,
    //   question: `What are the control statements?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 29,
    //   question: `Four types of functions?`,
    //   answer: ``,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 30,
    //   question: `Que es el DOM?`,
    //   answer: `DOM = Document Object Model o Modelo de documento objetos.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 31,
    //   question: `¿Para qué se utiliza el DOM?`,
    //   answer: `El DOM, se crea con la finalidad de poder identificar y permitirnos trabajar (modificando estilos, el contenido, añadiendo nodos hijos, etc) sobre todos los elementos (conocidos como nodos en DOM) de nuestro documento HTML.`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 32,
    //   question: `Para que sirve this?`,
    //   answer: `Sirve para tomar el nombre del objeto`,
    // },
    // {
    //   id: 33,
    //   question: `Que son los template String`,
    //   answer: `Los template string es una manera de concatenar string incrrustar valores o resultados de operaciones tambien para caracteres multilinea.`,
    // },
  ]
}

// Export data
export default data;

